WA 16296736.5

TIKO Entertainment, LLC Privacy Policy

Last Updated: March 25, 2021

TIKO Entertainment, LLC (“Tiko”, “we”, “us” or “our”) is committed to protecting the privacy of

your information. We believe it is a good business practice to disclose to you how your personal

information and activity on https://www.tikoofficial.com may be used. As a user of this website,

and its subpages and content (collectively, the “Site”) or the services or products (collectively,

“Service(s)”) provided by Tiko, this Privacy Policy is intended to describe in a straight-forward

and easily understandable manner:

• the information we collect about you;

• how that information may be used;

• with whom the information may be shared;

• how you may update the information you provide us;

• how you may contact us; and

• your choices about our uses and disclosures of your information.

As noted on the Terms of Use (“TOU”), by using the Site and/or Services you accept and

acknowledge that you are bound by this Privacy Policy. Accordingly, we encourage you to read

this Privacy Policy carefully. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy,

please feel welcome to contact us through our Site: https://www.tikoofficial.com/. Alternatively,

you can also e-mail us at contact@tikoofficial.com.

Information We Collect

We collect your information when you sign up for our newsletter, create an account, or purchase

a product through our Site. The information collected may include items such as your name, date

of birth, e-mail address, address, and phone number, as well as other information that may or may

not specifically identify you. The information collected on this Site may be stored at servers,

computers, or other media located in or outside the United States.

Third-Party Sources

We may obtain personal and non-personal information about you from third-party sources,

including referral sources. This information may be utilized, analyzed, and/or compared with

information that we have collected from you or that you have submitted to the Site. Such third

parties may include but are not limited to Google, Facebook, and other third-party referral sources.

If Tiko obtains information from third-party sources, Tiko takes reasonable measures to ensure the

third parties lawfully obtained and provided the information to us. If the third parties unlawfully

obtained and/or provided the information to us despite our reasonable measures to ensure the third

parties complied with all legal requirements in obtaining and providing the information to us, you

understand, agree, and acknowledge that your sole legal remedy is against the third party that

engaged in the unlawful activity and that you will not assert any cause of action, claim or demand

against Us.

WA 16296736.5

Information Collection Technology (Web Beacons and Cookies)

We may use various technologies to collect information from your electronic device about your

activities on our Site. We may collect and store non-personally identifying information through

cookies, log files, clear gifs (commonly known as “web beacons”), and third parties to profile user

activity and preferences. Technical and specification information about your browser and

computer is automatically collected when you use or visit the Site. This information may include

your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, your browser type, operating system, access time(s), the

content of previously accepted “cookies” from us, and the website address that referred you to our

Site.

A cookie is data stored on your computer that tracks non-personal information about you. When

using our Site, we may assign your computer one or more cookies that enable us to improve the

quality of our Service and to personalize your experience. Cookies allow us to automatically

collect information about your activity on our Site, such as the content you access while on our

Site, the links you click, and other activity you conduct while using our Site. You may choose to

modify your web browser’s setting to disable cookies or limit their use. If you choose to disable

or limit cookies, you are still able to access our Site, but you may be unable to use all of the features

on our Site. Additional information about cookies may be found at:

https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/260971/description-of-cookies.

Personal Information About Users Under 13 Years of Age Not Collected

The Site is meant for general audiences and not directed to children under the age of thirteen. We

do not intentionally collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen.

Nonetheless, this Privacy Policy is still designed to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy

Protection Act (“COPPA”) to the extent COPPA applies. We ask you to provide your date of birth

to help us comply with our COPPA legal obligations. If a user indicates they are under the age of

thirteen, we will prohibit the user from accessing the Site. If we obtain actual knowledge that we

collected or retained personal information about a child under the age of 13 without proper parental

approval, that information will be promptly deleted from our database, servers, and all other media.

Information Others May Collect

We partner with a third-party e-commerce company, Fanjoy Co. (“Fanjoy”), to give you the ability

to purchase our merchandise directly from the Site. In order to complete a transaction through the

Site, you will necessarily be redirected to a portion of the Site operated by Fanjoy. By agreeing to

this Privacy Policy, you hereby agree and consent to Fanjoy’s privacy policy found here:

\_https://shop.tikoofficial.com/pages/privacy-policy. Please review the Fanjoy Privacy Policy for

additional information on Fanjoy’s use, collection, and retention of your data.

To enhance security and promote operational efficiency, the Site utilizes the resources of reputable

hosting facilities that are controlled by third parties. Tiko is unable to provide any guarantees or

warranties about these third parties’ retention or usage of your information.

WA 16296736.5

Information Use and Sharing

We may use and share your information for any legally permissible purpose. We may match, use,

and share any of the information we collect from you to any personally identifiable information

we obtain through third parties. Examples of some ways we may use or share information that we

collect about you include:

• providing the Site and its contents to you;

• providing you with information, products, or services;

• providing you with customized content and services;

• providing professional support;

• communicating with you by e-mail, United States mail, telephone, text message, and/or

mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us,

any affiliates, sponsors or other third parties;

• enforcing our rights, contracts, or terms and conditions, or otherwise managing our

business;

• fulfilling any other purpose for which you provide it;

• complying with applicable legal and regulatory laws; and

• performing functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

In order to perform certain services on your behalf, we may publish certain information that you

provide. You agree that any testimonial feedback or other comments provided by you to TIKO

becomes the sole and exclusive property of TIKO and that such information may be used by TIKO

for any legally permissible purpose, including but not limited to marketing and advertising its

services and products.

You acknowledge and agree that TIKO may use and disclose your personal and non-personal

information to public or private third parties: (i) for inspection by law enforcement officials

(including in the case of potential criminal activity); (ii) to respond to cease and desist letters,

arbitration proceedings, legal actions and suits, criminal and civil subpoenas, any court orders; (iii)

to enforce or apply the terms of this Privacy Policy or any other agreement between us, including

the Terms of Use; and (iv) to protect the rights, property, or safety of Ours, our users, or others,

whether during or after the term of your use of our Services.

Third Party Privacy Policies May Be Applicable

Our Privacy Policy does not cover any third party’s use or handling of your information once it is

shared. Instead, the privacy policies of the third party(ies) will govern. We encourage you to visit

the websites of those third parties and fully read and understand their privacy policies.

Our Site may contain links to other websites, such as Fanjoy Co. found at shop.tikoofficial.com.

Tiko disclaims any responsibility for the privacy practices of third parties that may have links to

or from our website, or any framed content on our website. We encourage you to review the

privacy policies/statements of every website that you visit that collects personally identifiable

information.

Communications from Us

WA 16296736.5

Unless you opt out of certain communication features, we may use your information to

communicate with you, such as through e-mail, newsletters, and telephone. You may opt out

and/or unsubscribe to communications from Tiko at any time. See the Opt-Out Provisions and

Updating Your Information, below for applicable contact information and directions.

Your Information Will Not Be Sold

We will not sell any information you submit to us to any unrelated third-party without prior written

notice to you and an opportunity to opt-out.

Opt-Out Provisions and Updating Your Information

We value our user’s privacy and provide them with the option to “opt-out” of having their

information used for purposes not directly related to our Site. The opt-out option is available at

the time you sign up for your account. If you wish to change your opt-out preference or update

your information after you initially sign up for your account, you can opt-out by sending a

written request to us via email at: contact@tikoofficial.com.

Your request will generally be responded to within three (3) business days if your inquiry is via

e-mail, or thirty (30) days if your inquiry is via United States mail.

Please note that changing your opt-out preference will only affect future activities or

communications from us. In other words, if we already provided your information to a third party

before you changed your opt-out preferences, you will need to contact the third party directly. To

opt-out of communications from our third party business partners, if any, please contact them

directly.

Information Retention and Security

We may store your information for more than one (1) year from the time of initial submission, as

well as automated personal information we collect about you.

We take reasonable security measures to protect users’ information against unauthorized access,

loss, alteration, or destruction. Despite these reasonable measures, we cannot guarantee our

security measures are impenetrable. Therefore, although we take reasonable steps to secure your

information, we cannot and do not promise or warrant that your information will always remain

secure.

Visitors Outside the United States

This Privacy Policy is intended to cover collection of information on our Site from residents of the

United States. The laws in other countries may or may not be as comprehensive as those in the

United States. If you are a resident of another country and/or are visiting our Site from outside the

United States, you acknowledge and agree that your information may be transferred to, stored, and

processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated.

You also acknowledge that your use of the Site or our Services shall be governed exclusively by

the laws of Missouri and as if all transactions take place within Missouri. By using our Site, you

acknowledge and agree that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third

WA 16296736.5

parties with whom we share it as described in this Privacy Policy. If you are unwilling to accept

these terms, then you agree that you will not use or access the Site or our services.

Privacy Policy Updates and Revisions

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. We reserve the right to modify the Policy

at any time without notice, so please review the Policy frequently. When changes are made to this

Policy, we will revise the “last updated” date at the top of this Privacy Policy. If we make any

material changes in the way we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will also

post notice of the changes on our Site and/or may notify you by sending an e-mail to the e-mail

address you most recently provided us in your account. Your continued use of our Site or Services

after we have posted any Privacy Policy changes indicates your agreement to the changes unless

you notify us otherwise.

If you wish to retain a copy of this privacy policy, you should print a copy for your records. From

your web browser, this can be accomplished by selecting “download” or “print” from the

dropdown menu.

General Contact:

Tiko Entertainment, LLC

PO Box 14910

Springfield, MO 65814
